[Five years ago, Tianjiu Alley]
What are you doing here?
Why?
Do you own Tianjiu Alley?
Am I not allowed here?
Only poor people live here.
They are not rich young masters like you.
They don't have time to play with you.
I'm warning you.
If you dare to make fun of them,
I'll...
You'll what?
Hit me?
Come on.
Hit me right here.
You...
What exactly do you want?
I can do whatever I want.
Do you think you're a cop,
who can mind everyone's business?
Shen.
Is Lu here?
Let go.
Do you want her to see us fighting?
Lu.
Lu, you're here.
Granny.
Here is the delivery this time.
Please take it.
Thank your father for me.
He knows our life is not easy.
He often sends things over.
Thanks for your hard work.
It's nothing, Granny.
I'm just running errands.
Shen, you're also a good boy.
You always come to the alley to help.
Thanks to both of you.
Granny, if there's nothing else,
I'll leave first.
Don't go.
Today, you both have to stay for dinner
before you leave.
I'll go cook for you.
Come.
Sit, sit, sit.
Sit down.
Sit.
You guys have a good chat.
Just because you're a good guy,
you don't have to
apologize for wronging me?
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Who cares?
[Eclipse in the Lost City] [Episode 9]
You should know better than me
who lives in Tianjiu Alley.
Or have you forgotten because it's been
so long since you worked as a cop?
You're still protecting him
after all this?
Yes.
Why?
Do I need a reason?
Of course.
He's from the Shisha Gang.
So am I.
I must take him away today.
What if I refuse?
No. 7 Liutiao Lane in the western suburbs.
Uncle Zhong's
wife and daughter live there,
right?
What do you want?
Two lives for his one.
It seems Xu Qingdao isn't all that good
at keeping his men in line.
The rules of the underworld say
families are off-limits.
Officer Shen,
if I remember correctly,
when you were a cop,
you were all about the rules.
How come you've regressed
after joining a gang?
Young Master Lu,
you don't need to worry about my affairs.
Targeting women and children.
Shen Tianbai,
do you have no shame?
One word.
Are you going to make this deal or not?
From your tone,
it sounds like
you already know the answer.
Of course.
You dare to gamble with your own life,
but not with theirs.
Fine.
I'll make this deal.
But
street deals go by street rules.
He entered my territory
and beat up my men.
I can spare his life.
But whatever injuries my men suffered,
he has to pay back in full.
Two ribs.
Not one less.
I...
Will you do it, or should I?
I'll do it.
Okay.
I'll pay for him.
You are really loyal.
Alright.
Then I'll grant your wish.
Come here.
Do I have to teach you
how to take a beating?
I accept it this time.
I misjudged you.
-Tianbai.
Keep an eye on them.
Without my permission,
no one makes a move.
But next time,
I will definitely kill you.
Get lost!
Young Master.
Uncle Zhong.
I'm really sorry.
I brought trouble to your family.
What are you talking about?
Young Master, don't worry.
My wife is fine.
Don't worry.
Have a seat.
How much did you drink?
A little bit.
A little bit?
This...
You call this a little bit?
All right,
I'll go make you some hangover soup.
Uncle Zhong.
What's wrong, Young Master?
Tell me,
why do people become
what they hate the most?
Forget it.
I'm no better.
Young Master.
I have no right to judge him.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Tianbai.
You saved my life.
From now on,
your business is my business.
Just say the word.
Whether it's going through fire or water,
I'd be damned
if I said no.
Hui,
you're being too serious.
We are both from the Shisha Gang.
It's the least I could do.
Drink this bowl of wine,
and we are like real brothers.
Drink.
Cheers.
Good.
Great.
Seeing you like this,
I am very pleased.
Tianbai,
after you've rested for a few days,
how are you feeling?
Thank you, Chief.
I feel much better.
It's good to be young.
I should have
let you rest for a few more days,
but there is an urgent matter right now.
Since Hui is injured,
I can only leave this to you.
Go ahead.
Here's the thing.
Mr. Smith, the boss
of Taigu Foreign Liquor Store,
commissioned us to deliver a few boxes
of high-end foreign liquor to Jiangcheng,
for Mr. William, the director
of the Jiangcheng
Industrial and Commercial Bureau.
I'm leaving this matter to you.
Is that a problem?
No problem.
Good.
Chief,
I'll go prepare first.
After someone is injected
with the wolf toxin,
the closer it gets to the full moon,
the sharper their 5 senses become.
Wound healing accelerates,
and they recover far better
than ordinary people.
To alleviate the wolf toxin,
a maintenance dose
must be injected every half month.
No. 1.
Strange.
Why would the maintenance doses
be different?
No. 2 is darker than No. 1.
And that person clearly
took the maintenance dose.
Why was he still tormented
by the wolf toxin to the point of suicide?
Why did this happen?
[Lu Mansion]
Young Master, you're awake.
Uncle Zhong.
Help me contact someone.
I need to give him a push.
Chief!
I don't know what tricks
that brat Lu Ye used
to convince Smith
to let him go on the escort mission.
Damn it!
This is our business!
What are you panicking for?
Why?
Are you afraid of him?
Me?
Afraid of him?
Since he wants to go,
let's make sure he never returns.
Lu Wenbiao,
your son brought this upon himself.
-Extra! Extra!
-Boss.
-This is the news we found.
-All the latest news
out of Ningcheng!
Come and take a look!
Extra! Extra!
All the latest news out of Ningcheng!
What are you looking at?
What are you doing here?